Department of Chemistry fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Chemistry fonds
1965 - 1986
F-6
2.5 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Chemistry
The Department of Chemistry at Simon Fraser University was founded in 1965 as a charter department in the Faculty of Science. The Department has been responsible, through its Head, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in organic, inorganic, physical, theoretical, nuclear chemistry, as well as biochemistry. It became known for its breadth of programs and was unique in Canada for its involvement in the nuclear field, which is commonly found in physics departments.
The Department offered degrees at all levels from the beginning. Honours and majors degrees in Chemistry are awarded at the B.Sc. level and after a separate program in Biochemistry was instituted in 1968, similar honours and majors degrees in Biochemistry were added. In addition, minor programs are offered in all areas. A joint program with the Physics Department in Chemical Physics was initiated early in the history of the Department, and in the early 1980s, a joint Nuclear Science minor program with the Physics Department was started. An undergraduate cooperative education program began in 1982.
Administratively, the Department began with a Head of Chemistry who was appointed without term. In 1968 this was changed to an elected Head which, in turn, was changed to a Chair in 1972. In addition to the elected Departmental Tenure Committee, there were 3 main standing committees charged with the responsibility of ensuring the smooth and effective operation of the Department's business. They were the Undergraduate Studies Committee, the Graduate Studies Committee, and the Appointments Committee, which also acted as a long-range planning committee. These committees were appointed by the Chair and, in the case of the Undergraduate and Graduate Committees, had separate chairs. There were additional minor committees such as the Space Committee and the Safety Committee. Departmental operations were also assisted by Academic Advisors in Chemistry and Biochemistry, and the Graduate Admissions Officer. The Laboratory Coordinator (formerly the Departmental Assistant), helped with many administrative tasks.
The Department has been involved with TRIUMF (Tri-University Meson Facility) since its establishment in 1974, which marked the beginning of a major local research program in the nuclear sciences and associated areas. A long-standing research collaboration with members of the Department of Biological Sciences, called the Chemical Ecology Research Group, was formed in 1981.
During the Department's first year 12 faculty members were appointed. After an initial rapid increase in the next few years, the Department had a relatively stable number of 26 permanent faculty members by 1986.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
The fonds of the Department of Chemistry consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. Also included are the records of the Canadian Council of University Chemistry Chairmen. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curricula and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, an external review, faculty files, memoranda, minutes of meetings, and reports.
The records have been arranged into eighteen series in an order chosen by the archivist because the original order was not apparent. In some cases series consist of only one file. In others, records which appeared to fall under the same function, such as proposals for programs, were united under one series because this appeared to reflect how they were originally maintained. The above arrangement was also decided upon in order to facilitate intellectual access to the documents. In devising this arrangement, the archivist consulted the file classification system of the Department of Chemistry.
Jones, Colin H. W.; Wells, Edward J.; Bell, Tom N.; Tuck, D. G.; Pate, Brian D.
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Department between 1981 and 1989.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed as of September 2002 (33 cm., 1983-1988). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventory of the Faculty of Science fonds, F-24.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Annual reports, 1977 - 1982; F-6-1; 3 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of annual reports of the Department.
  Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Report of chemistry department, 1977; F-6-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Annual Report of Chemistry Department, 1980 - 1981; F-6-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
  - Annual Report of Chemistry Department, 1981 - 1982; F-6-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
- Awards to students, 1972 - 1983; F-6-2; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to student awards, including letters of recommendation, award notifications information.
  - Awards to students, [ca 1972] - [ca 1983]; F-6-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
- Budget, 1966 - 1979; F-6-3; 8 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the disbursement of funding within the Department, including salary issues. It includes correspondence and financial statements.
  - Budget applications, 1966 - 1968; F-6-3-1; 1 cm of textual records
    - Budget applications, 1966 - 1968; F-6-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
  - Salaries, 1968 - 1979; F-6-3-2; 7 cm of textual records
    - Salaries - chemistry laboratory instructors, 1970 - 1979; F-6-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
    - Salaries - faculty, 1968 - 1970; F-6-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
    - Salaries - faculty, 1971; F-6-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
    - Salaries - faculty, 1972; F-6-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
    - Salaries - faculty, 1973; F-6-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
    - Salaries - faculty, 1974; F-6-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-1)
- Canadian Council of University Chemistry Chairmen, 1974 - 1986; F-6-4; 27 cm of textual records
  Series consists of materials relating to the participation of the Department Chair in the Council. It includes agenda, minutes, correspondence and reports. Department Chair C.W. Jones served as Secretary-Treasurer of the Council from 1982-1985, and as Council Chair from 1985.
  Council of Canadian University Chemistry Chairmen
  - CCUCC, vol. 1, 1974; F-6-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, vol. 2, 1974; F-6-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, vol. 3, 1974; F-6-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, 1975; F-6-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, 1976; F-6-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, 1977; F-6-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, 1978; F-6-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, 1979 - 1980; F-6-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-2)
  - CCUCC, 1981; F-6-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 6-3)
  - CCUCC, 1982; F-6-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 6-3)
  - CCUCC, 1983; F-6-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 6-3)
  - CCUCC, 1984; F-6-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 6-3)
  - CCUCC, 1983 - 1985; F-6-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 6-3)
  - CCUCC, 1985; F-6-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 6-3)
  - CCUCC, 1986; F-6-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 6-3)
  - CCUCC, 1986; F-6-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
- Chairman's Search, 1974 - 1975; F-6-5; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of memoranda concerning the appointment of a Department Chair.
  - Chairman's search, 1974 - 1975; F-6-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
- Committees, 1967 - 1986; F-6-6; 59 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records of Department committees. It includes agenda, minutes, correspondence and associated papers.
  - Appointments, F-6-6-1; 1 cm of textual records
    Access to records in the subseries "Appointments" and "Departmental tenure" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
    - Appointments committee, F-6-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
  - Departmental tenure, 1967 - 1979; F-6-6-2; 43 cm of textual records
    - Tenure - drafts and committee papers, 1968 - 1969; F-6-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
    - Salary promotion and tenure, 1968 - 1969; F-6-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
    - Minutes, 1970; F-6-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
    - Recommendations of the Department of Chemistry on tenure, promotion and contract renewal, 1970; F-6-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
    - Minutes, 1971; F-6-6-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
    - DTC material, 1971; F-6-6-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-4)
    - Minutes, 1972; F-6-6-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - DTC material, 1972; F-6-6-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - Minutes, 1973 - 1974; F-6-6-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - Salary review, 1973; F-6-6-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - DTC material, 1973; F-6-6-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - Minutes, 1974 - 1975; F-6-6-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - DTC material, 1974 - 1975; F-6-6-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - Salary review, 1974; F-6-6-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 6-5)
    - Minutes and agenda, 1975; F-6-6-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Salary recommendations, 1976; F-6-6-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Faculty salaries, 1976; F-6-6-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Minutes and notices of meetings, 1976; F-6-6-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Annual update and personal data forms, 1976; F-6-6-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Minutes, agenda and personal data forms, 1977; F-6-6-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Salary recommendations, 1977 - 1978; F-6-6-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Salary reviews, vol. 1, 1978; F-6-6-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 6-6)
    - Salary reviews, vol. 2, 1978; F-6-6-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - Minutes, 1978 - 1979; F-6-6-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - Salary tables, 1978 - 1979; F-6-6-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - DTC material, 1979; F-6-6-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - DTC procedures and criteria, 1972; F-6-6-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - University Tenure Committee, 1967 - 1974; F-6-6-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - Renewal, Tenure and Promotion - Policy and Procedure, 1972 - 1973; F-6-6-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - Rules and Regulations on Promotion, Tenure and Contract Renewal, 1968 - 1969; F-6-6-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - President's Advisory Committee on Faculty Salaries, 1975; F-6-6-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
  - Graduate curriculum, 1982 - 1985; F-6-6-3; 3 cm of textual records
    - Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1982; F-6-6-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1983; F-6-6-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
    - Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1984 - 1985; F-6-6-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
  - Safety, 1981; F-6-6-4; 1 cm of textual records
    Department of Chemistry. Saftey Committee
    File may contain personal or confidential information. Access to the files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Safety Committee, 1981; F-6-6-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-7)
  - Undergraduate studies, 1975 - 1986; F-6-6-5; 10 cm of textual records
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1975; F-6-6-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1977; F-6-6-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1978; F-6-6-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1978 - 1979; F-6-6-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1981; F-6-6-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1982 - 1983; F-6-6-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1984; F-6-6-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
    - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1985 - 1986; F-6-6-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
- Curricula and programs, 1969 - 1983; F-6-7; 16 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to new courses and programs in Chemistry. It includes program proposals and correspondence.
  - Chemical Education Program, 1969 - 1979; F-6-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
  - Clinical Chemistry Proposals, 1975; F-6-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-8)
  - Co-operative education, 1980 - 1983; F-6-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Continuing Education (DISC Program, Evening Programs), 1972 - 1975; F-6-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Continuing Education (DISC Program, Evening Programs), 1976 - 1978; F-6-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Course proposals and faculty changes, 1975 - 1978; F-6-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Proposed New Analytical Program, 1977; F-6-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Proposed new programs - engineering, 1979; F-6-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Proposed new programs - engineering, 1980; F-6-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Proposed new programs - engineering, 1981; F-6-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 6-9)
  - Proposed new programs - engineering, 1981; F-6-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
- Dean's correspondence, 1977 - 1981; F-6-8; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence between the Department Chair and the Dean of Science on a variety of issues.
  - Dean's correspondence, 1977 - 1981; F-6-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
- Grants - NSERC, 1986; F-6-9; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence from the Department Chair to other faculty members and the Dean of Science concerning the position of the Chair and the Canadian Council of University Chemistry Chairmen (CCUCC) on the review of NSERC programs.
  Council of Canadian University Chemistry Chairmen; Natural Science and Engineering Research Council
  - NSERC programs, 1986; F-6-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
- Liaison, 1969 - 1986; F-6-10; 29 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to liaison activities of the Department with schools, industry, and research foundations and facilities. It includes correspondence, memoranda, conference materials, proposals, and reports.
  - Liaison - colleges and high schools, 1969 - 1986; F-6-10-1; 15 cm of textual records
    Chemistry Articulation Committee
    - Chemistry in the '80s, 1980; F-6-10-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - Chemistry in the '80s, 1981; F-6-10-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - Chemistry in the '80s, 1982; F-6-10-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - Chemistry in the '80s, 1983; F-6-10-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - Chemistry in the '80s, 1984; F-6-10-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - Chemistry in the '80s, 1985; F-6-10-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - Chemistry in the '80s, 1986; F-6-10-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - College liaison, 1978 - 1980; F-6-10-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - Committee on articulation of College and University chemistry, 1972 - 1976; F-6-10-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - High school liaison, 1978 - 1981; F-6-10-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 6-10)
    - High school liaison, 1982 - 1985; F-6-10-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
    - Transfer credit with other institutions, 1969 - 1973; F-6-10-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
    - Transfer credit with other institutions, 1974 - 1978; F-6-10-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
  - Liaison - industry, 1974 - 1985; F-6-10-2; 5 cm of textual records
    BC Hydro; CIL
    - B.C. Hydro Research and Development, 1980 - 1985; F-6-10-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
    - CIL distinguished visiting lectureship - correspondence, 1974 - 1977; F-6-10-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
    - CIL distinguished visiting lectureship - programs, 1978 - 1981; F-6-10-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
  - Liaison - research foundations and facilities, 1970 - 1984; F-6-10-3; 10 cm of textual records
    National Research Council; TRIUMF
    - NRC - super conducting NMR facility, 1974 - 1976; F-6-10-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
    - Regional Facility, 1980 - 1984; F-6-10-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-11)
    - Slowpoke reactor, 1980 - 1981; F-6-10-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
    - Slowpoke reactor proposal, 1981; F-6-10-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
    - Slowpoke reactor, 1982; F-6-10-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
    - TRIUMF misc. correspondence, 1970 - 1977; F-6-10-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
- Meetings, 1965 - 1977; F-6-11; 28 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to meetings of the Department and the physical chemists group in the Department. It includes agenda, minutes, and associated papers.
  - Departmental meetings, 1965 - 1977; F-6-11-1; 27 cm of textual records
    - Departmental meetings, 1965; F-6-11-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-6-11-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-6-11-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-6-11-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-12)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-6-11-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1967; F-6-11-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1967; F-6-11-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1967; F-6-11-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1968; F-6-11-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1968; F-6-11-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1969; F-6-11-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1969; F-6-11-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1969; F-6-11-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1970; F-6-11-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1970; F-6-11-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 6-13)
    - Departmental meetings, 1971; F-6-11-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    - Departmental meetings, 1971; F-6-11-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    - Departmental meetings, 1972; F-6-11-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    - Departmental meetings, 1973; F-6-11-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    - Departmental meetings, 1974; F-6-11-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    - Departmental meetings, 1974; F-6-11-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    - Departmental meetings, 1975; F-6-11-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    - Departmental meetings, 1976 - 1977; F-6-11-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
  - Physical Chemists meetings, 1976 - 1977; F-6-11-2; 1 cm of textual records
    Department of Chemistry. Physical Chemicists
    - Physical Chemists (meetings), 1976 - 1977; F-6-11-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
- Plans and reviews, 1972 - 1979; F-6-12; 2 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to planning and the external evaluation of the Department.
  - Departmental plans, 1979; F-6-12-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
  - Departmental review, 1972; F-6-12-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
- Printed materials, 1965 - 1986; F-6-13; 9 cm of textual records
  Series consists of newsletters, news releases, and publications of the Department related to the promotion of programs and facilities.
  - Chemistry Newsletter, 1977 - 1980; F-6-13-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
    Open
  - Chemistry Communications, vol. 1-3, 1980 - 1982; F-6-13-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-14)
  - Chemistry Communications, vol. 4, 1983; F-6-13-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
  - Chemistry Communications, vol. 5, 1984; F-6-13-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
  - Chemistry Communications, vol. 6, 1985; F-6-13-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
  - Chemistry Communications, vol. 7, 1986; F-6-13-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
  - Chemistry Department Safety Manual, 1983; F-6-13-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
  - Miscellaneous publications, 1965 - 1986; F-6-13-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
- Radiation safety, 1979 - 1980; F-6-14; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to radiation safety in the facilities of the Department. It includes memoranda, policy and procedure documents, and reports.
  - Radiation safety, 1979 - 1980; F-6-14-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
- Student Union, 1977; F-6-15; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence between the Simon Fraser Student Society and the Chemical Sciences Student Union.
  Simon Fraser Student Society; Chemical Sciences Student Union
  - Student union, 1977; F-6-15-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
- Teaching, 1973 - 1985; F-6-16; 20 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to instruction in the Department. It includes correspondence, course evaluations, transcripts, and examination papers.
  Access to records in the subseries "Course evaluations" and "Student cases" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Course evaluations, F-6-16-1; 8 cm of textual records
    - Evaluations - A-D, F-6-16-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
    - Evaluations - E-J, F-6-16-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
    - Evaluations - K-O, F-6-16-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-15)
    - Evaluations - P-W, F-6-16-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Evaluations - B, F-6-16-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Evaluations - H, F-6-16-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Evaluations - P, F-6-16-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Evaluations - S-Y, F-6-16-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
  - Examinations and course outlines, 1980 - 1985; F-6-16-2; 8 cm of textual records
    - Examinations and course outlines - undergraduate 000-200 level, 1980 - 1981; F-6-16-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-16)